export const Data2 = [
    {
      question: 'How much GPA is required to study in Canada from Nepal?',
      answer: 'If you want to study in Canada, you should aim for a GPA of 2.8 or higher.'},
        
    {
      question: 'What is the cost of studying in Canada?',
      answer: 'The cost of studying in Canada will vary depending on the institution you choose and the program you enroll in. On average, international students can expect to pay between $15,000 and $30,000 per year for tuition.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Can i stsy in Canada after i graduate?',
      answer: ' Yes, after you graduate from a designated learning institution in Canada, you may be eligible to apply for a post-graduation work permit, which allows you to work in Canada for a period of time that is related to the length of your study program. This can help you gain Canadian work experience and potentially qualify for permanent residence in Canada.'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Is it easy to find a job in Canada after studying?',
      answer: 'After completing your studies in Canada, you may be eligible to apply for a work permit, which will allow you to work in Canada for a specific period of time.'},
        
    {
      question: 'Can i work while studying in Canada?',
      answer: 'Yes, as a study permit holder, you are allowed to work part-time on campus and full-time during scheduled breaks. However, you will need to obtain a work permit in order to work off campus.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Is student life easy in Canada?',
      answer: 'The Canadian way of life is enriching and rewarding for international students from all over the world. Canadian universities and colleges are filled with world-class facilities, sports, extracurricular activities, and cultural programs.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Are there scholarships available for international students in Canada?',
      answer: ' There are many scholarships available for international students who are studying in Canada. Scholarships can be offered by the Canadian government, educational institutions, or private organizations. The availability and eligibility requirements for scholarship and determine which ones you may be eligible for.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the process for obtaining a student visa extension?',
        answer: 'To obtain a student visa extension, you will need to apply to the Australian Department of Home Affairs. You will need to provide evidence that you are still enrolled in a full-time course of study and meet the necessary health and character requirements.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Why does a visa get rejected in Ausrtalia?',
        answer: ' While the vast majority of visa applications are approved, a visa application may be rejected for a variety of different reasons, including ineligibility, a lack of evidence or documentation, character issues, health concerns, and fake documents.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Can Nepali students apply for permanentresidency in Canada after graduating?',
        answer: ' Yes, after graduating from an Canadian educational institution, Nepali students may be eligible to apply for a temporary graduate visa, which allows them to work in Canada for up to four years after graduation. This can provide a pathway to permanent residency in Australia.'
      }


  ];
